WARNING: THIS APP IS CURRENTLY IOS ONLY

First, if you already have downloaded this before, go into your applications folder and delete the old app by dragging it into trash.

Now in Google Drive, right click the PokemonAdventures.app folder and click the download button at the bottom. Now, on the bottom right you will see it says "zipping 1 file". Wait for that to complete and then save the zipped file. Now open that zip file by double clicking, and you will get the app, which has an icon on it. You can now dispose of the zip by dragging it into the trash. Then, drag it into your applications folder. If it asks for an administrator password, type it in. Optionally, drag it into your application doc on the bottom of your screen for ease of use. Then, just double click and bam! There you go.