How to open this file on Mac
Apple does not support opening jar files with the double click on mac, so instead you have to open it in the terminal.

First, open the terminal app, which you can find under applications.

Then type 'java -jar' followed by the location of your file and it's name. For me, I keep it under downloads, so I would write something like this:

java -jar downloads/Game.jar

Finally, press enter, and a few seconds later, a java application should open up.
