To run this Java project, you must have the latest version of Java and the latest JDK (Java Development Kit)

Java:
Mac: https://www.java.com/en/download/apple.jsp
Scroll to the bottom and click "Download Java Mac OS X Version 10.7.3 (Lion or Newer)"

Windows: https://www.java.com/download/ie_manual.jsp
Scroll to the bottom and hit "Download Java" (the green button)

JDK:
https://www.oracle.com/java/technologies/downloads/#jdk18-mac

Download the one suited to your computer. The page you will be linked to it the Mac section, but you can click on the Linux or Windows if you aren't using a mac. Click on the x64 installer.
